Guide to the Administrative Papers of the President George Bugliarello RG.006
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series I: Subject Files, 6
  - Subseries B: MetroTech Center, 14
    - Research & Development 1 – Shapin, Jan C., 1980; 1204 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Research & Development 1 – Shorter, Charles A., 1980-1982; 1205 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Research & Development 1 – Stout, Gary E., 1980; 1206 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Research & Development 1 – Yulish, Morton & Associates Inc., 1980-1982; 1207 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Research & Development 2, 1980-1983; 1208 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Research & Development 2 – KBS Development Association, 1982; 1209 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Research & Development 2 – Natkins, Stanley, 1982-1983; 1210 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Research & Development 3, 1982-1983; 1211 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Research & Development 4 – New York Committee Trust, 1982-1985; 1212 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Scher, Seymour, 1976 December-1981 May; 2002 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Scher, Seymour, 1981 July-1990 April; 2003 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Polytechnic Corporation Planning Committee, 1983 February 9; 2005 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Board of Directors, 1993 May; 1213 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Metrotech Pamphlet, Undated; 1214 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Clippings, 1982-1985; 1215 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Metrotech Center, 1992-1993; 1216 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Metrotech Center - Design Guidelines, Undated; 1217 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Subseries C: Gramercy Steam Pipe Explosion, 15
    In the evening of Saturday August 19, 1989, a 24-inch Con Edison steam pipe under Gramercy Park at Third Avenue and 20th Street in Manhattan exploded, releasing an eruption of steam and debris, killing three and injuring nineteen. Days later, hundreds of residents in nearby apartment were evacuated from their homes after air quality tests showed extremely high levels of asbestos fibers which blanketed nearby buildings after the explosion. George Bugliarello was appointed by Mayor Edward I. Koch to chair a task force of representatives of Con-Edison, city officials and consulting engineers, to investigate the facts and circumstances surrounding the explosion.
    - Gramercy Park Explosion – Miscellaneous, 1989 August-1991 May; 1230 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Gramercy Park Steam Explosion - Department of Environmental Protection, 1989-1990; 1231 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Gramercy Park Steam Explosion, 1990 July; 1232 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Gramercy Park Steam Explosion – Lawsuit, 1988; 1233 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Gramercy Park Steam Explosion – Lawsuit, 1989 November 1; 1234 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Gramercy Park Steam Explosion – Technical Report – Lucius Pitkin, 1990 January; 1235 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Commission on Cause of August 19, 1989 Gramercy Park Steam Explosion – Final Report, 1990 July; 1236 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Gramercy Park Interviews – Volume 1 of 5, 1990 January 16; 1237 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Gramercy Park Interviews – Volume 2 & 3 of 5, 1990 January 18; 1238 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Gramercy Park Interviews – Volume 4 of 5, 1990 January 23; 1239 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Gramercy Park Interviews – Volume 5 of 5, 1990 January 24; 1240 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Gramercy Steam Pipe Explosion - Miscellaneous, 1990 March-April; 5769 (Box 17.1, Folder 1)
    - Gramercy Steam Pipe Explosion - Miscellaneous, 1989-1990; 5770 (Box 17.1, Folder 2)
    - Gramercy Steam Pipe Explosion - Miscellaneous, 1989-1990; 5771 (Box 17.1, Folder 3)
    - Gramercy Steam Pipe Explosion - Task Force - 1, 1989-1990; 5772 (Box 17.1, Folder 4)
    - Gramercy Steam Pipe Explosion - Task Force - 2, 1989-1990; 5773 (Box 17.1, Folder 5)
    - Gramercy Steam Pipe Explosion - Task Force - 3, 1989-1990; 5774 (Box 17.1, Folder 6)
- Series II: Bern Dibner Library / CATT, 8
  This series contains architectural, administrative, and financial reports and charts regarding the planning, development and construction of Bern Dibner Library and the Center for Advanced Technology in Telecommunications (CATT) at 5 Metrotech Center.
  This series is maintained in its original order with original folder titles.
  - AETC Environmental Consultants, 1989; 757 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Relocation Services, 1991 October-November; 758 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Shared Publications – 1.8.1.2, 1989 February-1990 August; 759 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - CAD VLSI Instructional 1.1.1.8 & CAD VLSI Research 1.2.3, 1989 February; 760 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - CAT/CS Computers 14, CS Small computers and special projects 1.1.2.2, 1.1.2.4, 1989 April-1990 August; 761 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Image Processing - 1.2.2, 1989 February, 1990 July; 762 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Fellows & Offices, 1989 February-May; 763 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - CATT Demo Facility, 1.2.12 & Office Automation, 1.2.6, 1989 November, February; 764 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Communications & Computer System 1.2.1, 1989 February; 765 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Optics instructional, 1.1.1.10; Optics research 1.2.7; Dark room, 1989 January-1990 October; 766 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - EE Labs, 1.1.1.1., 1.1.1.6, 1.1.1.2, 1.1.1.7, 1.1.1.3, 1.1.1.11; EE Lab Support, 1.3, 1.5, 1987 March-1991 February; 767 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Acoustics 1.2.8, 1989 February-1990 August; 768 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Millwork Revisions Library - August 24, 1990, 1991 April-May; 769 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Millwork Revisions Library - August 24, 1990, 1990 August-1991 February; 770 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building Environmental Assessment, 1989 December-1990 July; 771 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Committees, 1986 January-1991 September; 772 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Architect, 1985 December-1992 February; 773 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Engineering, 1988 August-1992 December; 774 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Program Investigation for Center for Advanced Technology in Telecommunications, 1987 January; 775 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Program – Library, 1987 October-1992 March; 776 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Program – Library, 1985 October-1991 January; 777 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - A Proposal to Provide Preconstruction and Construction Management Services, 1987 February 6; 778 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Statement of Credentials, 1987 January 28; 779 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Program – CATT, 1988 June-1992 April; 780 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Program – CATT, 1985 March-1988 June; 781 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Operation & Management, 1986 July-1992 July; 782 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Utilities, 1989 April-1992 October; 783 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Flood Damage & Claim, 1991 August-1993 July; 784 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Consultant Agreement, 1989 July-March; 785 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Additional Building Items, 1991 October-1994 April; 786 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Library / CATT Building Owner's Costs, 1990-1992; 787 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Morse Diesel, 1991 May-1992 April; 788 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Morse Diesel, 1992 May-1993 February; 789 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Farmingdale Septic Tank, 1966; 790 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Farmingdale Loan Agreement, 1962; 791 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Poly Dorm Bonds of 1962 – Master, 792 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Request for Dorm Loan from Housing & Home Finance Agency, 1962 October-November; 793 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building - Building Signage, 1991 October; 794 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Morse Diesel Monthly Job Progress, 1990 July-September; 795 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Morse Diesel Monthly Job Progress, 1990 May-June; 796 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Polytechnic Library Building Program Draft, 1984 August 30; 797 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Farmingdale Housing, 1989 May-1990 February; 798 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Long Island Campus Pre-Fab, 1988 April-1990 January; 799 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - L.I.C. Mortgage Equipment & Furnishings Industry, 1985 June-1989 February; 800 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Farmingdale Campus - Space Electronics Institute, 1988 February-June; 801 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Long Island Architects, 1988 February-April; 802 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Farmingdale Campus Survey Prepared by Bohn & Bonacci, 1987 October-1989 August; 803 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Steven J. Hyman Association Engineering Drawings & Blue Prints, 1982, 1989; 804 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Record of Invoices L.I.C. (Long Island Campus) Dorm Project, 1989-1991; 805 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - L.I.C. Dorm Project 1989-1991, Owner, 806 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - L.I.C. Dorm Project, 1989-1991; 807 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Reports – Construction Meetings – 1962-1963, 1962 December-1963 November; 808 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Proposal to U.S. Office of Education, L.I.C., 1965 March 29; 809 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Farmingdale Construction Bids, 1962; 810 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Antennae Range – L.I.C., 1963; 811 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence – L.I.C. – 1962-1964, 812 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Cullen & Dykman – L.I.C., 1962-1964; 813 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Payroll Records – L.I.C., 1963; 814 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Insurance Certificates – L.I.C., 1962-1964; 815 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Housings & Home Finance Agency, 1962-1964; 816 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Dormitory – L.I.C., 1963-1964; 817 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Publicity – L.I.C., 1963 January-February; 818 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Punch List – L.I.C., 1963-1964; 819 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Physical Planning Bulleting – L.I.C., 1962-1963; 820 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Sketches – Photographs – L.I.C., 1962-1964; 821 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Bills – L.I.C. Construction Account, 1962-1963; 822 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Eggers & Higgins – L.I.C., 1959-1965; 823 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Survey – L.I.C., 1962 December-1963 January; 824 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Approvals – L.I.C., 1962 December-1963 July; 825 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Contract Payments – Ross Wein Inc. – L.I.C., 1962 August-1966 June; 826 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Ross-Wein Inc. – L.I.C., 1962 December-1965 March; 827 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Schedules – L.I.C., 1963 January 2; 828 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Sykes, Galloway & Dykman (Attorneys) – L.I.C., 1963 January-1964 January; 829 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Construction Management – Dibner / CATT, 1991 February-December; 830 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Construction Management – Dibner / CATT, 1987 May-1991 February; 831 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Library / CATT Architects Fee, 1990 January-1992 November; 832 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Library / CATT Architects Fee, 1986 October-1989 December; 833 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Library / CATT building – Owner's Costs II – Additional / Professional Services – 6A-6C, 1988-1992; 834 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Library / CATT building – Owner's Costs II – Additional / Professional Services – 6D-6F, 1988-1992; 835 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Library / CATT building – Owner's Costs II – Additional / Professional Services – 6G, 1988-1992; 836 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Library / CATT building – Owner's Costs II – Additional / Professional Services – 6H – Others – 1 – 5, 1988-1992; 837 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Library / CATT building – Owner's Costs II – Additional / Professional Services – 6H – 6-14, 1988-1992; 838 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Library / CATT building – Owner's Costs II – Additional / Professional Services – 6H (15), 7, 1988-1992; 839 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Library / CATT Trade Awards, 1988-1992; 840 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Library / CATT Trade Awards, 1988-1992; 841 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Morse Diesel – Final Working Drawing Budget, 1989 July, 1990 September; 842 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Morse Diesel – Design/ Development Budget Cost Savings / Value Engineering, 1989 July 28; 843 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1991 July; 844 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1991 June; 845 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1991 May; 846 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1991 March-April; 847 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1991 February; 848 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1991 January; 849 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1990 December; 850 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1990 November; 851 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1990 October; 852 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1990 September; 853 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1990 August; 854 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building Telecommunications Invoices, 1989 February-1992 September; 855 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Dibner / CATT – Construction Bulletin, 1990 June-1991 April; 856 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Dibner / CATT – Punch Cards, 1992 January-May; 857 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Dibner / CATT – Punch Cards, 1992 January-March; 858 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Dibner / CATT – Interface Architectural Signage, Inc., 1989 November-1992 May; 859 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Union Gas (B.U.G.) Company, 1983 January-1984 September; 860 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Union Gas (B.U.G.) Company, 1978 January-1983 January; 861 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Cush & Wake (Real Estate), 1983 June-1984 August; 862 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising, 1986 October-1988 May; 863 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising, 1984 December-1986 December; 864 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Library Development, 1985 October-1986 December; 865 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Library Development, 1984 May-1985 October; 866 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Library Development, 1981 December-1984 March; 867 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Metro Tech Center (M.T.C.) State Legislation – General, 1981 December-1982 March; 868 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Originals – M.T.C., 1985 September-1988 November; 869 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Originals – M.T.C., 1983 July-1986 March, Undated; 870 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Dibner / CATT – General, 1987 January-December; 871 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Dibner / CATT – General, 1988 January-December; 872 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - M.T.C. – State Assistance – General - #1, 1981 January-1982 August; 873 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - M.T.C. – State Assistance – General - #2, 1982 October-1983 April; 874 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Dibner / CATT – Reports of Gift - Dibner Fund, 1984 January-1991 February; 875 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Dibner / CATT – Reports of Gift, 1983 October-1989 December; 876 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Dibner / CATT – Reports of Gift - Dibner Fund, 1979 August-1990 October; 877 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans - CATV5, E101, 1989-1990?; 878 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – AV 6-8, CATV 1-6, PA 1-3, 1989-1990?; 879 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – P-100-501, 1990; 880 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – E-401-502, SP-100-101, 1990; 881 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – AV 6-8, CATV 1-6, PA 1-3, 1989-1990; 882 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – SK-MW 1-15, 1991; 883 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – SK-MW 16-45, 1989-1990?; 884 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A-100-107, 201-206, 211-212, 1990; 885 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A-301-309, 311-316, 321-322, 1990; 886 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A-331-333, 401-404, 411-412, 421-422, 431-433, 501-502, 511-513, 1990; 887 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A-521, 551-554, 561-563, 581-582, 601-605, 801, 901-902, 1990; 888 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – S-1-12, 101-105, 107, 1990; 889 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – M-001, 101-106, 201, 301-302, 401-403, 1990; 890 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Dibner / CATT - Floor Plans - M501-502, E001, E101-106, E301, L101-105, 1990; 4559 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – SK-MW 1-10, 1990; 891 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – SK-MW 11-20, 1991; 892 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – SK-MW 21-30, 1989-1990?; 893 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – SK-MW 31-40, 1989-1990?; 894 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – SK-MW 41-45, 1989-1990?; 895 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A-561-563, 581-582, 1989-1990; 896 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A-601-605, 801, 901-902, 1990; 897 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – S-1-8, 1990; 898 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – S-9-12, 101-105, 1990; 899 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – S-107, M-001, 101-106, 1990; 900 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – M-201, 301-302, 401-403, 501-502, 1990; 901 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – L-101-103, 105, P-001, 101-102, 1990; 902 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – P-104-106, 301-303, 1990; 903 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – P-401, 501, SP-001, 101, E-001, 1990; 904 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – E-101-106, 1990; 905 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – E-301, 401, 501-502, 1990; 906 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A101A, 103A-B, 601A, 603A-B, November 1990; 907 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A101-107, 201, 1990; 908 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A202-206, 211-212, 1990; 909 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A301-308, 1990; 910 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A309, A311-316, 1990; 911 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A321-322, 331-333, 401-403, 1990; 912 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A404, 411-412, 421-422, 431-432, 1990; 913 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A433, 501-502, 511-513, 521, 1990; 914 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A551-554, 1990; 915 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Dibner / CATT – Security System Specifications, 1990 January 15; 916 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Dibner / CATT – Sheet Waterproofing, 1990 February 1; 917 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Dibner / CATT – Section 2 – Table of Contents – 15501 Thru 15519, 1990 February 1; 918 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Dibner / CATT – Section 4 – Division 17 – Table of Contents – 17100 Thru 17200, 1990 February 1; 919 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Dibner / CATT – Section 1 – Division 15 – Mechanical, 1990 February 1; 920 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Dibner / CATT – Division 16 – Electrical – 16010 Thru 16931, 1990 May 23; 921 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Dibner / CATT – Architect's Summary of Audiovisual Basebuilding Requirements, 1989 December 19; 922 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Dibner / CATT – Section Listing – Construction Specifications, 1990 February 1; 923 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Dibner / CATT – Telecommunications Library – Architectural Standards, 1988 August-October; 924 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Dibner / CATT – Telecommunications Library 1988 – Cable Standards, 1988 August; 925 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Dibner / CATT – Invoices – Preconstruction, 1988 September-1989 August; 926 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Dibner / CATT - Plan for CATT submitted to New York State Science & Technology Foundation - Part 1, 1993 September; 927 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Dibner / CATT - Plan for CATT submitted to New York State Science & Technology Foundation - Part 2, 1993 September; 928 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook 1, Preconstruction – 1989 – 1, 1988-1989; 929 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook 1, Preconstruction – 1989 – 2, 1988-1989; 930 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook 1, Preconstruction – 1989 – 3, 1989-1989; 931 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook 1, Preconstruction – 1989 – 4, 1988-1989; 932 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook II – 1, 1988-1990; 933 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook II – 2, 1991 February-October; 934 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook II – 3 – Architects, 1989 December-1991 October; 935 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook II – 4, 1990 February-November; 936 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Dibner / CATT – Controlled Inspection Reports – 1, 1990-1991; 937 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Dibner / CATT – Controlled Inspection Reports – 2, 1990-1991; 938 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Dibner / CATT – Controlled Inspection Reports – 3, 1990-1991; 939 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Dibner / CATT – Controlled Inspection Reports – 4, 1990-1991; 940 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Dibner / CATT - 1987-1988, 941 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Dibner / CATT – Physical Inventory, 1990-1991; 942 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Dibner / CATT – Library Equipment & Furnishings, Invoices, 1990-1992; 943 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Dibner / CATT – Non-Building Costs, Invoices – 1, 1992-1993; 944 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Dibner / CATT – Non-Building Costs, Invoices – 2, 1990-1993; 945 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #1 – 1, 1990; 946 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #1 – 2, 1990-1991; 947 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #1 – 3, 1990-1991; 948 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #2 - 1, 1990-1991; 949 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #2 – 2, 1990-1991; 950 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #2 – 3, 1990-1991; 951 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #3 - 1, 1990-1992; 952 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #3 - 2, 1990-1991; 953 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #3 - 3, 1990-1991; 954 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #4 – 1, 1990-1991; 955 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #4 -2, 1990-1992; 956 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #4 -3, 1991-1992; 957 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building – Design Development – 1, 1989 May-July; 958 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building – Design Development – 2, 1989 May 22; 959 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building – Design Development – 3, 1989 May 22; 960 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building – Addendum – 1, 1990 February; 970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building – Addendum – 2, 1990 February; 971 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building – Addendum – 3, 1990 February; 972 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Dibner / CATT - Oversize floor plans, 1988, 1992; 961 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Dibner / CATT - Oversize floor plans, April 1990 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Series III: Polytechnic, 7
  This series contains documents pertaining to George Bugliarello's administration as University President and includes correspondence, memoranda, pamphlets, and other promotional material highlighting George Bugliarello's administrative, development and fundraising efforts on behalf of Polytechnic.
  This series is arranged topically into 7 subseries.
  - Subseries A: Honorary Degrees, 1957-1986; 1218
    - Honorary Degrees, 1980-1981; 1219 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1982; 1222 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1983; 1223 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1984-1985; 1220 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Honorary Degrees - Gaertner, Dr. Wolfgang W., 1985 November; 1856 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Honorary Degrees - Nominations, 1980-1987; 1221 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Honorary Degrees - Nomination, Proposals, Undated; 1224 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Honorary Degrees - Educational Committee, 1984-1985; 1227 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Honorary Degrees - Miscellaneous, 1957-1979; 1225 (Box 27, Folder 9)